RACHELLE ADAMS

770.881.2242 | adamsrachelle@icloud.com | linkedin.com/in/adamsrachelle

PROFILE

Experienced office administrator and empathic civil servant with a keen aptitude for efficiency and organization. Demonstrated capacity for learning skills quickly and applying them effectively. Pursuing professional development opportunities that engage both sides of the brain.

EXPERIENCE

OFFICE ASSISTANT | CITY OF SMYRNA GOVERNMENT | SMYRNA, GA | 8.2020-PRESENT

Assist public with inquiries and procedures related to building permits and inspections, code compliance/enforcement, and business licensing. Process and issue residential and commercial permits, including: building, roofing, mechanical, and temporary signage permits. Prepare daily inspection lists for Chief Building Official and building inspectors. Compile weekly status reports for City administration. Perform administrative functions for department staff.

SCHEDULING COORDINATOR | ATLANTA ARBOR | MARIETTA, GA | 8.2016-8.2020

Manage production calendar to meet and exceed daily revenue goals. Responsible for route planning, equipment allocation, and timely scheduling of client projects. Organize permitting to ensure compliance with city and county ordinances. Provide administrative support to company management. Serve as front desk reception and first point-of-contact for clients and vendors.

SALES LEAD | LANE BRYANT | KENNESAW, GA | 8.2014-7.2016

Build and retain clientele through consultative sales and product expertise. Train staff in customer service and operational best practices to increase KPI growth. Analyze store performance data to identify sales opportunities and develop team strengths. Manage back office administration to comply with monthly audits. Promoted from Sales Associate in October 2014.

FLOOR SUPERVISOR | GARDEN RIDGE | KENNESAW, GA | 8.2012-8.2014

Direct store operations related to inventory management and visual merchandising. Train new hires in warehouse safety procedures to comply with OSHA standards. Perform administrative functions to support management in fast-paced retail environment. Maintain office organization, supply inventory, files, databases, and confidential records. Promoted from Sales Associate in January 2013.

EDUCATION

KENNESAW STATE UNIVERSITY | BBA, ECONOMICS | MINOR, FILM STUDIES | 2012

SKILLS

Office management, Project management, Data entry, Data analysis, Event planning, Social media, Content development, Customer service, Team leadership, Employee training, Sales, Research, Windows, macOS, Microsoft Office, Apple iWork, Google G Suite, QuickBooks, Munis